isoftstone.com 2019-03-09

# iSoftStone-Privacy

**Committed to Protecting Privacy**

iSoftStone is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to activities directly related to your visit of the iSoftStone website. It does not apply to third parties' websites linked through the iSoftStone website. We strongly recommend that you read these third parties' privacy policies prior to providing any information to such sites. iSoftStone has no responsibility or liability in connection with any third parties' websites.

**Collection, Use and Transfer of Your Information**

You can visit most of the iSoftStone site without disclosing your personally-identifiable information ("personal data"). However, you may choose to provide us with your personal data, for example when you contact us, register for seminars, activities and programs available on our website or when you request information or services. 

You also may decide to provide us voluntarily with personal data of a third person, such as your spouse, colleague or friend. In such case, we assume that you have unrestricted permission from such person to provide his/her personal data to iSoftStone. 

iSoftStone may use suppliers to collect, process, store, use, analyze and/or transfer the data on its behalf. In such case, it is iSoftStone practice to require that these suppliers handle the personal data they process or transfer in a manner consistent with iSoftStone's policies. By submitting personal data to us, you acknowledge and agree with your data being processed and/or transferred on iSoftStone's behalf by its suppliers. 

iSoftStone will handle the information we learn from you from your visit to our website in the following manner:

  * **If you visit our site to read or download information, such as news, product information, case studies or articles:**

We may collect, process or transfer only the following information about you: the name of the domain from which you access the Internet; the date and time you access our site; and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site. We use the information we collect to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, and to help us make our site more useful to visitors. We may use "cookies" and/or technologies to collect personally non-identifiable information from your visits to our website to enhance your overall site experience and for statistical purposes. You can set your browser to turn off "cookies" or to warn you when a website attempts to place a "cookie" on your computer. However, if you turn off the "cookies", some websites may not work properly. 

  * **If you submit personal data when visiting a iSoftStone website:**

We may collect, process and/or transfer the specific information you voluntarily provide to us in the contact form you choose to fill in on our website, including the personal data you provide. By submitting any personal data on iSoftStone's site, you authorize iSoftStone to use, process and transfer (if necessary across borders) such data, even in and to countries where the level of data protection may not be commensurate with the high standard of protection adopted by certain countries, such as the standard suggested by the EU Data Protection Directive. In such countries, iSoftStone will still handle your personal data in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. iSoftStone will not sell personal data to third parties; however your personal data may be automatically transferred to the successor to substantially all of the assets and business of iSoftStone.

  * **If you are a client, or are part of a client organization, or are a subcontractor:**

Personal data you provide to iSoftStone, including personal data of a third party, such as your spouse, colleague and friend may be collected, stored, used and transferred as necessary for iSoftStone to carry out business or seek potential business in the future with your company. If you provide us with personal data, whether in the form of an e-mail, business card, orally during business meeting or otherwise, we assume that you have granted us a permission to collect, store, use and transfer such information with no limitations even in and to countries where the level of data protection may not be commensurate with the high standard of protection adopted by certain countries, such as the standard suggested by the EU Data Protection Directive. We also assume that you have unrestricted permission from the third party for the transfer of its personal data.

  * **Disclosure Required by Law:**

Please be aware that it is possible that personal data you provide to iSoftStone may be subject to disclosure under the law (e.g. pursuant to a statutory provision, a court order or a subpoena).
